galaxylovenote.com 2012-05-25

# Samsung GALAXY Love Note

## Privacy Policy

Protein take the responsibility of not only printing and posting your cards, but also of being guardians of the personal information that you give us, extremely seriously. We believe that you have a right to privacy and to control your personal information. The following legal document will dictate how we will handle this information.

This privacy policy together with our terms of use sets out how Protein Limited, ("we", "our", "us") will use any personal data we collect from you, or you provide to us during your use of the online service (the "website").

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits the website. Our policy on the collection and use of personal information is outlined below.

We collect and use personal information in order to:

  * Administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement that you may have with us.
  * Anticipate and resolve problems with your service.

In order to carry out the above, we may need to collect and process personal information about you (including but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, email address, details of your visits to the website and any transactional information in relation to order fulfillment). We may ask you for this information on the website during the purchase process or at any subsequent point. The data we collect may be provided to Data Processors for analysis so that we may tailor the products, services and marketing materials we, and other third parties, offer to you (where you have consented to receive the same).

In order to take advantage of some of our services, you may need to supply us with the personal details of a third party (for example, their name and address if you wish to send them some of Touchnote"s products ("the product")) via the website. We will not use this information for anything other than providing the service for which the information was supplied. 

We will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless:

  * We are legally entitled to do so (for example, pursuant to a court order or for the purposes of prevention of crime or fraud). You will be treated as having given your permission for disclosures referred to in this policy.
  * We, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * To enforce or apply our terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, safety, customers, or others.

### Non-Personal Details

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you, such as the type of browsers you use or the website from which you linked to us. This information is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on the website. We may, from time to time, supply the owners and operators of third party websites which have a link to our site with information about the number of users linking to the website from their website. You cannot be identified from any of this information. 

### Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report information to our branded partners.

We may store some information on your computer when you visit the website. This information facilitates your use of the website, and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details on each visit. The information may be stored in a cookie which is required for the shopping basket and other e-commerce facilities to function. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which allows you to choose whether or not to accept it, however switching off cookies may result in the website having dramatically reduced functionality including, but not limited to, being able to shop on the site. We do not have any control over cookies which our advertisers or branded partners may use on the website. 

### Security

The technology that we use and the policies that we have implemented are intended to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use. We will continue to update these measures as new technology becomes available. 

### Your Rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes, or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us (use the Feedback tab). 

### Links

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Contact us

If you would like to contact us regarding any of the areas of this policy and website, please do so at [info@proteinos.com](mailto:info@proteinos.com).

Last updated 10 January 2012
